<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:polar="http://mediavoice.com/schema" xmlns:mvcf="http://mediavoice.com/schema/refinery29" version="2.0"><channel><title>Refinery29</title><language>en-us</language><description>Refinery29</description><link>http://www.refinery29.com</link><category>Refinery29</category><atom:link rel="self" href="http://www.refinery29.com/newscred.xml"/><atom:link rel="next" href="http://www.refinery29.com/newscred.xml?page=2"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 15:57:21 +0000</pubDate><link rel="hub" href="http://refinery29.superfeedr.com/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"/><link rel="self" href="http://www.refinery29.com/newscred.xml" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"/><item><title>A Lesson In Imperfection</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>I scroll through my phone like everyone else. I see the world filtered and duckfaced like every other woman does. And sometimes I’m almost convinced that’s real.</p><p>But it’s not.</p><p>The curated lives we see every day are fake. The perfect angles, the perfect outfits, the perfect lighting. That’s not reality. What is real are imperfections. What builds character and toughness is struggle. What makes us better and more human is attempting something, coming up short, and then trying it again.</p><p>But for women the rules seem different.</p><p>Men get the luxury of being able to specialize. Women are expected to be perfect at everything.</p><p>Am I good girlfriend? Am I a perfect mom? Am I the best athlete? Am I wearing white after Labor Day? Am I dressed in the right brands? Am I dieting right? Am I manicured, blown-out and tanned?</p><p>These little constant quests for perfection start pecking away at our attention. Perfect never leaves room for improvement. And perfect never lets us focus on what’s really out there for us to achieve.</p><p>When we worry about perfection, our bigger goals are sacrificed. We can’t look up, work hard and kick ass. But having the confidence to ignore the perfection around us can be difficult.</p><p>When I was growing up in North Dakota, before my family moved to Los Angeles, I was a tomboy. I wore jeans and a white T-shirt, but not the sexy kind. I wore it because I loved to run, jump, and play. Dresses got in the way of that.</p><p>Then we moved to L.A., where I was a complete outsider. I went to a predominantly Spanish-speaking school, and never really fit in. My confidence sank faster than I care to admit.</p><p>And like most girls, although women rarely talk about it, these feelings came to a boiling point when I stood in front of the mirror, looked at my changing body that I didn’t really recognize anymore, and cried.</p><blockquote>I wasn’t perfect, and I didn’t like it.</blockquote><p>I wasn’t perfect, and I didn’t like it.</p><p>That’s when I found judo.</p><p>When you practice judo, you have to have a partner. Suddenly the quiet girl had to talk or get thrown on her ass. That was a fast and effective lesson in confidence.</p><p>Not every move I made was perfect, but I practiced a lot. And the world didn’t end when I talked or even yelled. In fact, I got better and people started noticing.</p><p>Today I have a career built on something that saved me as a young woman. Many women aren’t afforded that opportunity.</p><p>And when I see little girls rocking their jellies and tutus in the supermarket, I think about the unapologetic confidence I used to have in my jeans and T-shirts. That’s before I started trying to be perfect, and well before I found a passion that embraced my flaws and gave me shots at redemption.</p><p>I’m not trying to inspire you take up martial arts or be anything you’re not. But there was a time in your life when you didn’t care about being perfect. Maybe you didn’t quite understand the way the world worked then, but you also didn’t care what anyone thought.</p><p>I guess what I’m trying to tell you is that <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116412/reebok-perfect-never-ronda-rousey">you don’t need to be perfect to be valid</a>.</p><p>Your flaws — your unsuccessful attempts at greatness or even mediocrity — are real. They make you better. And that’s beautiful because it’s never perfect.</p><p><em>It's your body. It's your summer. Enjoy them both. <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/take-back-the-beach">Check out more #TakeBackTheBeach here</a>.</em></p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116843/joy-bryant-beautiful-model-personal-story" title="Girl, You Beautiful"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/20e/x/1621684/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117045/gonorrhea-resistant-antibiotics" title="Gonorrhea May Soon Be Untreatable "><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/3dc/x/1622424/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116874/biting-nails-immune-system-benefits" title="This Gross Childhood Habit May Have An Unexpected Benefit"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/087/x,80/1622114/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Ronda Rousey</dc:creator><publishedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 14:40:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 15:39:25 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/229/1200x900,80/1623167/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Quiz: Can You Complete These &lt;em&gt;Clueless&lt;/em&gt; Quotes?</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/clueless-movie-trivia-quotes?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/clueless-movie-trivia-quotes?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>If the movie <em>Clueless</em> were a human, she would now legally be able to drink — not that age would have stopped her before.</p><p>Amy Heckerling's iconic 1995 film has reached its 21st birthday. We can only hope that to this day, kids are still saying "ugh, as if" to gropey high school boys everywhere. Of course, there are many quotable moments and zings that fans will always remember. Our personal favorite? The late Brittany Murphy pulling off the best diss ever: "You're a virgin who can't drive."</p><p>So to test your '90s knowledge (and allegiance to Cher), we've rounded up some of the most iconic quotes from the film. Do you really know what Tai accused Dionne of doing? What about Cher's totally clueless interpretation of Christian's obsession? Cliff's Notes can't help you with this quiz (though IMDb definitely can). Click through to test your knowledge, and let us know your answer — and favorite quote! — in the comments below.</p><script type="text/javascript" src="//cdn.playbuzz.com/widget/feed.js"></script><div class="pb_feed" data-embed-by="64f9d497-3c98-4886-9102-dbd62189c99e" data-game="/Refinery29/quiz-can-you-complete-these-clueless-quotes" data-recommend="false" data-game-info="false" data-comments="false"></div>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116379/best-movie-soundtracks" title="Our Favorite Movie Soundtracks Of All Time "><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/21f/x/1622178/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117192/the-girl-on-the-train-trailer" title="Emily Blunt Loses Her Mind In &lt;em&gt;The Girl On The Train&lt;/em&gt;"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/be6/x,80/1623246/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117152/wonder-woman-director-gal-gadot" title="This Is Why &lt;em&gt;Wonder Woman&lt;/em&gt; Needs A Female Director"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/392/x,80/1622854/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Jessica Chou</dc:creator><publishedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 12:30:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 13:45:42 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/fd1/1200x900,80/1623106/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>8 Things You Need To Know This AM</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/117160?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/117160?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/2ca/1200x900/1571835/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure><p><h3>1. Here At Home: Lt. Brian Rice has been acquitted of all charges connected to the death of Freddie Gray.</h3></p><p>Rice had been charged with involuntary manslaughter, reckless endangerment, and misconduct in office. Prosecutors alleged that Rice had caused Gray's death last year by failing to fasten him in a seat belt in the back of the police van, where he suffered severe spinal-cord injuries. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2015/12/99694/trial-death-freddie-gray-brian-rice-acquitted">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>2. Major News: Russian athletes could be banned from competing in the 2016 Olympics over a doping cover-up by the Russian government.</h3> The call comes after a Russian involved in the 2014 Sochi Games cover-up came forward to detail how performance-enhancing drug use by the Russian Olympians was concealed. (<a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2016/07/19/sports/report-confirms-state-sponsored-doping-by-russia-at-olympics.html?_r=1">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>3. World News: Over 100,000 Venezuelans visited Colombia this weekend in search of food and supplies they wouldn't find at home.</h3></p><p>The Venezuelan government opened the previously closed border between the two countries for a single Sunday for a second time on July 17. (<a href="http://time.com/4409902/venezuela-food-shortages-colombia/?xid=homepage">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>4. Talking Points: Omarosa Manigault, best known as a former contestant on <em>The Apprentice</em>, is now Donald Trump's director of African-American outreach.</h3> She said of the presumptive nominee, "Donald Trump is focused on improving the economic conditions of African-Americans in this country..." <a href="http://www.politico.com/story/2016/07/omarosa-trump-team-225717#ixzz4EnAOZERQ">(Read More</a>)</p><figure><img src="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/ff0/1200x900,80/1623244/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900"/><figcaption><span class="copyright">Photo: Matt Baron/BEI/Shutterstock.</span></figcaption></figure><p><h3>5. Just Wrong: Gov. Mike Pence wrote a review of <em>Mulan</em> in 1999, in which he criticized the idea of women in the military.</h3> Pence suggested the film proved men and women serving in the military together wouldn't be able to resist pursuing romantic relationships, saying, "Moral of story: women in military, bad idea." (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117092/mulan-women-in-the-military-mike-pence">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>6. ICYMI: <em>Game of Thrones</em> ' seventh season will premiere in summer 2017.</h3></p><p>HBO has announced that in addition to premiering later than it traditionally has, the series' seventh season will contain seven episodes instead of ten. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117145/game-of-thrones-season-7-production">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>7. A-List: Diane Kruger and Joshua Jackson have officially broken up.</h3> Reps for the two actors, who have been together for a decade, said in a statement, "Diane Kruger and Josh Jackson have decided to separate and remain friends." (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117169/diane-kruger-joshua-jackson-split">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>8. On The Trail: A portion of Melania Trump's RNC speech appears to have been plagiarized.</h3> Melania Trump's <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117094/melania-trump-speech-rnc-opening-night">highly anticipated debut</a> on the Republican National Convention stage has landed her in hot water. A section of her speech in which she praises her own parents is now under scrutiny for its similarities to first lady Michelle Obama's 2008 convention speech. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117202/melania-trump-plagiarize-michelle-obama">Read More</a>)</p><figure><img src="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2d3/1200x900/1571954/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/116880" title="8 Things You Need To Know This AM"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/32e/x,80/1621810/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/116401" title="8 Things You Need To Know This AM"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/13f/x,80/1619511/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/116171" title="11 Officers Shot, 5 Killed During Rally In Dallas, &amp;amp; More Stories"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/1df/x,80/1618672/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Us</dc:creator><publishedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 10:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 14:37:28 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/public/043/1200x900/1621842/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Here's What Happens To Your Body When You Have An Orgasm</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/what-is-an-orgasm?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/what-is-an-orgasm?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Sex is one of the basic pleasures of life, but the orgasm is anything but simple — especially for people with vaginas.</p><p>The complexity begins with your anatomy. While you probably know that generally, your journey to orgasm starts with vaginal or clitoral stimulation, you might not realize that there's <a href="http://www.bumc.bu.edu/sexualmedicine/physicianinformation/female-genital-anatomy/">still debate among researchers</a> about the exact anatomy of the clitoris. The most visible part of this intriguing organ is the small bundle of extra-sensitive nerve endings that sits right underneath where the two inner labia meet up top. From there, the clitoris actually <a href="http://www.museumofsex.com/the-internal-clitoris/">extends internally</a> in two shafts that sit along either side of the vagina. Experts may still be mapping the clitoris in full, but pretty much everyone understands the sexual purpose: pleasure.</p><p>To understand your orgasm, you should also know that the vaginal canal is lined with the soft tissue of the mucous membrane covering layers of stretchy muscle. (This canal leads to the cervix, a narrow passageway that sits in front of the uterus. This is the <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/sperm-pregnancy-myth">long journey</a> upon which sperm must embark in order to fertilize an egg. Some <a href="http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0003347283712728">research</a> suggests that the female orgasm may help improve your chances of getting pregnant by improving "sperm retention," but you have to time it right.)</p><p>During arousal, you'll notice your heart rate increase, your skin may begin to feel (and look) flushed, and your genitals will swell with blood. But you're also building up a lot of muscle tension throughout your body.</p><p>Once you reach orgasm, the muscles in your <a href="http://goaskalice.columbia.edu/answered-questions/violent-orgasms">vagina, anus, and uterus</a> involuntarily rhythmically contract and then relax. Hence that awesome feeling of "release."</p><p>At the same time, your brain is working up quite a potent cocktail of chemicals. That includes the neurotransmitter dopamine, which is commonly associated with <a href="http://neuroscience.mssm.edu/nestler/brainRewardpathways.html">pretty much anything that feels good</a>. But during an orgasm, you're also getting a huge release of oxytocin, which can promote feelings of closeness and empathy (among <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/love-chemical-oxytocin#slide">many other things</a>).</p><p>Also, according to a small <a href="http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/j.1460-9568.2006.05206.x/abstract">2006 study</a> published in the <em>European Journal of Neuroscience</em>, there's some evidence that, in women, the brain's hippocampus and amygdala show decreased activity during sex — but before climaxing.  Both of those areas are associated with emotional regulation, especially fear and anxiety. And, during orgasm, activity decreased in other brain areas, too. That suggests that feeling safe and relaxed may be especially important for women to reach an orgasm.</p><p>But every body is different, and there's <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/types-of-orgasms#slide">way more than one way to get to an orgasm</a>. What works for one person won't necessarily work for everyone else. The good news is orgasms all feel great. But the <em>better</em> news is that they come with plenty of <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/health-benefits-of-sex#slide">health benefits</a>, too.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/first-date-questions" title="8 Questions To Ask On A First Date"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/ad7/x,80/1227414/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photo: Courtesy of Cece Olisa.]]></media:credit><media:title><![CDATA[Opener]]></media:title></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/sex-toys-reviews" title="The Sex Toys You Didn't Know You Needed"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/840/x,80/1544644/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:title><![CDATA[Perstein-Lauren_R29-Shot3-Hotel-245 2]]></media:title></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116952/singles-dating-advice-meet-in-real-life" title="18 Stories Of Couples Who Met By Chance, No Apps Involved"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/c26/x,80/1622176/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Illustrated By Tristan Offit.]]></media:credit></link><dc:creator>Sarah Jacoby</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 22:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 13:57:51 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/d95/1200x900/1622230/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Lauren Perlstein.]]></media:credit></media:content></item><item><title>How Beauty Products Helped Me Combat My Trichotillomania</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/trichotillomania-remedy-beauty?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/trichotillomania-remedy-beauty?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>For five years, my morning routine rarely changed. I’d wake up with raw eyes, blurred vision, and a sore scalp. It’d take a few seconds to remember why. The reality would sink in after a quick glance in the mirror. There were bald patches between my lashes and brows — and I’d done it on purpose.</p><p>It wasn’t always this way. Much to the envy of my friends, I had a full set of thick, dark lashes and a mane that grew at an almost unstoppable rate. All the while, they obsessively checked whether theirs had reached shoulder-length or not. But secretly, I was battling trichotillomania.</p><p>At 16, stressed from upcoming exams at school, I started to pick out a few lashes here and there. Later, it escalated to my brows and the hair on my scalp. Although it did occur to me that it wasn’t quite "normal" (my identical twin sister was never affected by it), pulling hairs quickly became addictive. It wasn’t long before bald spots grew to the size of a quarter.</p><p>No matter how much I resolved to stop pulling, I couldn’t quite beat the thrill of looking at my desk and seeing hair scattered all over it.</p><blockquote>No matter how much I resolved to stop pulling, I couldn't quite beat the thrill of looking at my desk and seeing hair scattered all over it...</blockquote><p>Even so, I couldn’t ignore the downsides. Now that my hair was no longer attached to my body, I realized just how much of a powerful symbol of femininity it really was. I felt singled out — even ostracized — from the invisible club where women with hair (in the right places) were entitled to a lifetime membership.</p><p>I took offense to makeup ads on the subway and TV and skipped past the beauty sections of magazines. It was as if they were taunting me for having deliberately "de-womanized" myself. But most of all, I lived in constant fear of being discovered. There were countless 18th and 20th birthday group shots that I never appeared in. Most likely, I was lurking in dimly lit bathrooms, precariously balancing a pocket mirror and a spare tube of eyelash glue in the dull lights.</p><p>At my most desperate, I resorted to plucking out my pubic hair, as there wouldn’t be the typical tell-tale signs the next morning. Then, one day, my falsies fell off, revealing my baldness, and I had no choice but to come clean. Nothing could quite undo the sheer horror of that moment.</p><p>Overnight, my body had become public property — judged and scrutinized. I was initially met with a resounding chorus of "Why?" particularly among my friends who longed for lustrous lashes like the Bollywood icons they idolized; lashes I once had.</p><p>Some had even taken to the running joke: “How can you tell Salma and her twin sister apart? Salma’s the one without eyelashes." Most memorably, one person had likened it to "self-mutilation." I couldn’t help but see the comparisons. After all, I’d spend hours literally tearing the hair from my scalp, lashes, and brows, only to wake up the next morning, repulsed by what I’d done.</p><p>To my surprise, there was one emotion that overrode the humiliation: relief. I was unwittingly afforded the freedom I desperately craved. I was no longer enslaved by the ritualistic hourly mirror checkups or lugging countless tools in my bag. I certainly didn’t miss feeling forced to conform to society’s expectation of what a woman should look like.</p><p>But as the fifth anniversary of pulling edged closer, I discovered that makeup didn’t have to serve the functional purpose I once believed. Instead, it could be enjoyable and empowering. I experimented with MAC’s Russian Red and fell in love with Urban Decay’s powder blush. One moment, I could channel Twiggy’s doe eyes; the next, Kat Slater’s overdrawn lips. Those moments cemented my love for makeup (one I didn’t quite realize I had) and its transformative power.</p><p>Before long, I’d started spending countless hours perusing beauty counters, the same ones I had actively avoided. I soon discovered outweighed the thrill I got from pulling. Best of all, mornings were no longer a hellish extension of a late-night binge. Now, new products — not lashes — were jostling for space on my desk.</p><p>Like me, a new wave of trich sufferers are embracing beauty’s power to reclaim their bodies. Instead of hiding away like I once did, there’s been a surge in beauty bloggers who are no longer afraid to bare all (often quite literally) about the disorder.</p><p>Gweni, who runs <a href="http://www.gbeauty.co.uk">www.gbeauty.co.uk</a>, is one such blogger. Her tutorials — namely, eye makeup for no eyelashes — reveals just how much beauty products have been instrumental to her recovery. “Although makeup doesn't actually stop me from pulling, it does give me the confidence to leave the house without feeling like I look 'weird.' I don't want to draw attention to hair-pulling and it’s helped me achieve that.”</p><p>Meanwhile, Sophie, behind <a href="http://www.PrettyandPolished.co.uk">Pretty and Polished</a>, goes one step further, snapping photos without her lashes and brows. She explains: “There's a huge pressure to show a perfect life on Instagram, so it was almost fun to rebel against it and show the 'ugly' side of this disorder.” Even so, she’s yet to brave it offline: “Makeup is such an integral part of my life, to the extent I wouldn’t quite know where I'd be without it. Wearing false eyelashes and drawing on my eyebrows allows me to cover the disorder, hide the shame, and pretend to be 'normal'. It doesn’t solve trich or rid me of paranoia, but it certainly helps ease the stress.”</p><p>Today, I’ve all but beat the disorder. That’s not to say that recovery has been easy, nor that there’s a universal "cure" to it. There are still physical memories: I have patches of hair that never quite grew back and stubby lashes that still don’t curl, even after several layers of mascara. But I definitely don’t cower away from the beauty counter. Now, I’m the one hunting down the latest launches!</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117198/100-layers-of-foundation" title="100 Layers of Foundation Looks Just As Uncomfortable As It Sounds"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/d0a/x,80/1623266/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/halal-beauty-industry-certification" title="Move Over Organic, This Beauty Category Is Taking Over Cosmetics"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/184/x,80/1622586/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Shirley Yu. ]]></media:credit></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/foundation-dark-skin-tones" title="The Best Base Makeup For Women Of Color"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/c1f/x,80/1535048/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Janelle Jones.]]></media:credit><media:title><![CDATA[opener]]></media:title></link><dc:creator>Salma Haidrani</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 22:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 14:29:07 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/1f1/1200x900/1559951/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Brayden Olson]]></media:credit></media:content></item><item><title>How To Make A Caviar Hot Dog </title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/caviar-hot-dog-recipe-video?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/caviar-hot-dog-recipe-video?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<style type="text/css">
.schemaRecipeContainer{
font:12px Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;
}
.schemaRecipeContainer a{
color:#000;
}
.schemaRecipeName,
.schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader,
.schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformationFacts{
font-weight:bold;
font-size:16px;
display:block;
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader,
.schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader{
padding-top:10px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions{}
.schemaRecipeAuthor{
font-weight:bold;
}
.schemaRecipeDatePublished{
padding-left:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeDescription,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformation{
display:block;
padding:10px 0;
}
.schemaRecipePrepTime,
.schemaRecipeCookTime,
.schemaRecipeYield,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformation span{
display:block;
}
.schemaRecipeIngredients{
padding:0 0 0 18px;
margin:0;
}
.schemaRecipeIngredients li{
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions ol{
padding:0 0 0 18px;
margin:0;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions li{
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeCredits{
padding-top:10px;
}
</style><div itemscope="" itemtype="http://schema.org/Recipe" class="schemaRecipeContainer">
	<div class="schemaRecipeNameAuthorDate">
		<span itemprop="name" class="schemaRecipeName">Caviar Hot Dog </span>
		<span class="schemaRecipeDatePublished"><meta itemprop="datePublished" content="2016-7-18"></meta>July 18, 2016</span>
	</div>
	<span itemprop="description" class="schemaRecipeDescription">Caviar definitely isn’t on my usual shopping list. In fact, this was my first-ever caviar purchase. However, a friend had suggested caviar hot dogs as a way to elevate the all-American cookout food, and I decided I had to try them. What better way to give the classic hot dog a seriously fancy upgrade? Plus, since hot dogs are budget-friendly, this mashup doesn’t end up costing  much more than a typical meal.</span>
	<span class="schemaRecipePrepTime"><strong>Prep Time:</strong> <meta itemprop="prepTime" content="PT5M"></meta>  5 Minutes</span>
	<span class="schemaRecipeCookTime"><strong>Cook Time:</strong> <meta itemprop="cookTime" content="PT15M"></meta>  15 Minutes</span>
	<span class="schemaRecipeYield"><strong>Yield:</strong> <span itemprop="recipeYield">1</span></span>
	<div class="schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader">Ingredients</div>
		<ul class="schemaRecipeIngredients"><li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 hot dog, we like Hebrew National
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 hot dog bun
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				Ketchup, to taste
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				Mustard, to taste
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				Sauerkraut, to taste
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				Relish, to taste
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 small jar caviar
			</li>
		</ul><div class="schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader">Recipe Instructions</div>
	<span itemprop="recipeInstructions" class="schemaRecipeInstructions">
		<ol><li>
				Set the oven to broil  or preheat to 400°F.
			</li>
			<li>
				Broil hot dog for 15 minutes.<br></li>
			<li>
				Top with ketchup, mustard, sauerkraut, relish. <br></li>
			<li>
				Finish off with Caviar to taste.<br></li>
		</ol></span>
	<div class="schemaRecipeCredits"><a href="http://www.bbqislandinc.com/rich-snippet-recipe-markup-tool.html">Recipe Generator</a> courtesy of BBQ Island</div>
</div>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117196/instagram-food-drink-emoji" title="Instagram's Most Common Food &amp;amp; Drink Emoji Reveal We Really Like Booze"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/950/x,80/1623259/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117195/coloring-book-cookbook" title="Coloring Book Cookbooks Are A Thing Now"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/5e3/x,80/1623258/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117096/100-years-family-dinners-mode" title="Dine Back In Time With 100 Years Of Family Dinners"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/3cb/x,80/1622557/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Lauren Paige Magenta</dc:creator><dc:creator>Recipe by Lauren Paige Magenta</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 20:20:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 20:20:01 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/a87/1200x900,80/1622553/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://content.jwplatform.com/videos/6fiJqkra-r0yi2e87.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="30" height="1080" width="1920"><media:title><![CDATA[How to Make a Caviar Hot Dog]]></media:title><media:description><![CDATA[Not that the traditional hot dog needed it or anything, but we've kicked it up a dozen notches. Adding cavair to the top of your dog is an unexpected, way to enjoy a frankfurters this season]]></media:description><media:category>Food,Living,Rad &amp; Cheap,Recipe</media:category><media:thumbnail url="https://content.jwplatform.com/thumbs/6fiJqkra-720.jpg"/></media:content></item><item><title>8 Quotes That Show What Millennial Women Really Think About Money</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/money-diaries-saving-advice?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/money-diaries-saving-advice?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Last winter, we launched <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary">Money Diaries</a>, where twice a week, a millennial woman opens up about her spending and saving habits and tells all. While the women stay anonymous, we know everything about them, from how much they make to what they eat for breakfast to whom they go home with, and a million little details in between. It’s amazing how money touches every facet of our lives, and yet it’s something many of us are reluctant to talk about. The goal with Money Diaries is to break down this last taboo, and if the comments (good and bad) are any indication, it’s working.</p><p>Ahead, eight of our favorite lessons we learned about money from the past six months of Money Diaries. Surely there is more wisdom to be gleaned from the diaries still to come.</p><p><strong>Lesson 1: Budget For The Little Luxuries.</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-social-media-strategist-new-york-city">A Week In NYC On A $55,000 Salary</a></p><p><em>The social media strategist celebrating her birthday and budgeting for Starbucks.</em></p><p>Day 4:</p><p>I stop by Starbucks to pick up my latte that I have budgeted in three times a week. <strong>$4.84</strong></p><p><strong>Lesson 2: Tax Deductions Are Your Friend</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-san-francisco-cam-girl-budget">A Week As A Cam Girl On A $70,000 Salary</a></p><p><em>A cam girl in San Francisco stocking up on work supplies (lingerie, vibrators, and makeup).</em></p><p>Day 2:</p><p>This week is "upkeep week," so it's going to be a little more expensive than usual. I head to Victoria's Secret and get 15 pairs of panties, four bras, and a pair of sweats (the sweats are just for me). I keep tabs of these work expenses, so I can deduct them at the end of the year. <strong>$250</strong></p><p><strong>Lesson 3: Cooking At Home Is The Key To Saving Big</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-fashion-photographer-new-york">A Week In NYC On A $42,000 Salary</a></p><p><em>An entry-level fashion photographer prepping for a gallery show.</em></p><p>Day 7:</p><p>At Key Foods, I grab blueberries (on sale 2/$5!), two avocados, a cucumber, onion, half a dozen eggs, greek yogurt, chicken breasts, ground beef, salsa, and chips. <strong>$50</strong></p><p><strong>Lesson 4: Avoid Unnecessary Purchases</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-marketing-brooklyn-budget">A Week In NYC On A $91k Salary</a></p><p><em>A woman in Brooklyn buying birthday cards and sushi.</em></p><p>Day 4:</p><p>I go work out, but forget my water bottle, so I had to buy water. Such a waste of money. <strong>$2</strong></p><p><strong>Lesson 5: Sometimes It’s Okay To Splurge</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-architect-new-york-city">A Week In NYC In On A $100,000 Salary</a></p><p><em>An architect in NYC, spending her tax return.</em></p><p>Day 2:</p><p>I got my tax return earlier this week, so I've decided to go ahead and spend it on a few big purchases. I book a plane ticket for a summer trip with a friend. <strong>$249</strong></p><p><strong>Lesson 6: Don’t Let Bad Days At Work Lead You To Impulse-Spend</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-designer-new-york-city">A Week In NYC On A $65k Salary</a></p><p><em>A designer who eats her feelings — and goes on back-to-back dates.</em></p><p>Day 5:</p><p>I've been pretty unhappy and inundated at my job lately, so I impulse-buy a beauty treatment on Gilt City. Oops. <strong>$59</strong></p><p><strong>Lesson 7: Set Up Automatic Transfers To Save More Money</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-new-york-librarian-salary">A Week In NYC On A $45,000 Salary</a></p><p><em>A librarian buying concert tickets and taking a physics course on the side.</em></p><p>Day 1:</p><p>I have $25 automatically transferred to my emergency/long-term savings account, bringing it up to $3,260. My goal is to get it to at least $5,000, and most months I contribute something extra, but this is the minimum.</p><p><strong>Lesson 8: Actively Set Aside Savings For “Future Fun” Plans, Like Weddings</strong></p><p>From: <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-san-francisco-biotech-budget">A Week In San Francisco On A $115,000 Salary</a></p><p><em>A San Franciscan in biotech saving $1,500 a month for a down payment.</em></p><p>Day 6:</p><p>Book a rental car for a wedding we are going to in Hawaii in September, but it’s already been planned for in the “Future Fun” budget. At the beginning of the year, I tallied up the costs of all the trips, travel, weddings, major gifts, and expenses I knew I had to pay for, and then divided that by 12 to understand what I should be “saving” each month.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117171/paying-cash-benefits-research" title="Paying In Cash Hurts So Good, According To Research"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/89b/x,80/1622970/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117112/rich-kid-trust-fund-personal-essay" title="I'm The Trust Fund Baby You Love To Hate"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/ae1/x,80/1622603/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117046/benny-donates-100-bills-oregon" title="Mysterious Person Is Hiding $100 Bills In Cereal Boxes &amp;amp; Diaper Packages"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/753/x/1622422/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Lindsey Stanberry</dc:creator><dc:creator>Jessica Chou</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 17:50:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 23:14:36 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/ded/1200x900/1622751/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Annotated Lyrics: The Real Meaning Behind &quot;The Boy Is Mine&quot;</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/the-boy-is-mine-lyrics-meanings?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/the-boy-is-mine-lyrics-meanings?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><em>When you were a teenager, you didn't really think about the meanings of the words to your favorite songs. You just sang along — and possibly choreographed dances to them with your friends. And, since nostalgia and millennials are something of a package deal, it's likely that now you look back fondly on the songs of your adolescence as untouchable, perfect, not up for criticism. But have you ever stopped to think about what these songs are actually about? In our <strong>Annotated Lyrics</strong> series, we'll revisit No. 1 songs on their chart-topping anniversary to explore what the lyrics are really telling us.</em></p><p>On July 18, 1998, Brandy and Monica had a chart-topping duet. "The Boy Is Mine" played a central role in the formative years of '90s kids, and now it plays an equally important role on any #TBT playlist.</p><p>But, in retrospect, this song doesn't make a lot of sense.</p><p>Though the song — and the incredibly dated music video — holds a special place in our hearts, a closer look at the lyrics brings up a lot of valid questions. For starters, how did this conversation even take place? This was a time before social media and the ubiquity of cell phones with data plans. Did they just run into each other at the mall? Also, why are these women feuding with each other? It's pretty clear that the real enemy is this dude who's trying to date both of them.</p><figure><img src="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/8dd/1200x900/1622530/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure><figure><img src="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/4b8/1200x900/1622529/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117233/taylor-swift-best-friend-defends-her-death-threats" title="Taylor Swift's Childhood BFF Got Death Threats For Defending Her"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2aa/x,80/1623373/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117190/taylor-swift-pseudonym" title="Has Taylor Swift Given Up Her Pseudonym?"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/48c/x,80/1608525/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117167/taylor-swift-kanye-west-teams-celebrities-taking-sides" title="Taylor &amp;amp; Kim: A Guide To Which Celebs Have Chosen Sides"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/97c/x,80/1622953/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Vanessa Golembewski</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 16:00:01 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/509/1200x900/1622551/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How to Make Cookie Dough Brownies</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/cookie-dough-brownies-recipe-video?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/cookie-dough-brownies-recipe-video?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<style type="text/css">
.schemaRecipeContainer{
font:12px Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;
}
.schemaRecipeContainer a{
color:#000;
}
.schemaRecipeName,
.schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader,
.schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformationFacts{
font-weight:bold;
font-size:16px;
display:block;
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader,
.schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader{
padding-top:10px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions{}
.schemaRecipeAuthor{
font-weight:bold;
}
.schemaRecipeDatePublished{
padding-left:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeDescription,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformation{
display:block;
padding:10px 0;
}
.schemaRecipePrepTime,
.schemaRecipeCookTime,
.schemaRecipeYield,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformation span{
display:block;
}
.schemaRecipeIngredients{
padding:0 0 0 18px;
margin:0;
}
.schemaRecipeIngredients li{
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions ol{
padding:0 0 0 18px;
margin:0;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions li{
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeCredits{
padding-top:10px;
}
</style><div itemscope="" itemtype="http://schema.org/Recipe" class="schemaRecipeContainer">
	<div class="schemaRecipeNameAuthorDate">
		<span itemprop="name" class="schemaRecipeName">Cookie Dough Brownies</span>
		<span class="schemaRecipeDatePublished"><meta itemprop="datePublished" content="2016-7-15"></meta>July 15, 2016</span>
	</div>
	<span itemprop="description" class="schemaRecipeDescription">You know those indecisive baking moments when you absolutely cannot pick between making cookies or brownies? We have those moments often. So we figured the best thing to do was combine two of our favorite recipes. Do us a solid and try this cookie dough brownie that we lovingly nicknamed the #brookie. </span>
	<span class="schemaRecipePrepTime"><strong>Prep Time:</strong> <meta itemprop="prepTime" content="PT1H"></meta> 1 Hour </span>
	<span class="schemaRecipeCookTime"><strong>Cook Time:</strong> <meta itemprop="cookTime" content="PT25M"></meta>  25 Minutes</span>
	<div class="schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader">Ingredients</div>
		<ul class="schemaRecipeIngredients"><li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 box brownie mix
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 bag chocolate chips 
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1/2 cup flour
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 cup brown sugar, packed
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 tsp plus a few extra dashes vanilla extract
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1/4 tsp cinnamon
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				1 tbsp plus 1 splash soy milk
			</li>
		</ul><div class="schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader">Recipe Instructions</div>
	<span itemprop="recipeInstructions" class="schemaRecipeInstructions">
		<ol><li>
				Make your favorite boxed brownie mix according to the package instructions. Once baked, let cool. (We followed the moist brownie instructions, but chewy works, too!)
			</li>
			<li>
				 In a separate bowl, mix together flour and brown sugar.  <br></li>
			<li>
				Add ½ the package chocolate chips, cinnamon, and vanilla. Stir to combine.
			</li>
			<li>
				Mix in soy milk. A little moisture goes a long way, so use your judgement. If the dough is too sticky, add a little flour; and if you need more moisture, more milk!
			</li>
			<li>
				Use your hands to press the dough into a ball. Place the dough into a Ziplock bag (or wrap in plastic wrap) and chill in the fridge until cold (approximately 1 hour).
			</li>
			<li>
				On a floured surface (like a cutting board or marble countertop), roll out the chilled dough to match the size of the top of your brownie.  
			</li>
			<li>
				Melt the rest of the chocolate chips (setting aside a small handful for later) in a glass bowl in the microwave. (Microwave for 30 seconds, stop, stir, and repeat until chocolate is fully melted.)
			</li>
			<li>
				Drizzle half the melted chocolate over the top of the brownie and then place the rolled out cookie dough on top.
			</li>
			<li>
				Drizzle the rest of the melted chocolate over the cookie dough and sprinkle over the reserved handful of chocolate chips.
			</li>
		</ol></span>
	<div class="schemaRecipeCredits"><a href="http://www.bbqislandinc.com/rich-snippet-recipe-markup-tool.html">Recipe Generator</a> courtesy of BBQ Island</div>
</div>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117196/instagram-food-drink-emoji" title="Instagram's Most Common Food &amp;amp; Drink Emoji Reveal We Really Like Booze"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/950/x,80/1623259/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117195/coloring-book-cookbook" title="Coloring Book Cookbooks Are A Thing Now"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/5e3/x,80/1623258/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117096/100-years-family-dinners-mode" title="Dine Back In Time With 100 Years Of Family Dinners"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/3cb/x,80/1622557/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Lauren Paige Magenta</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:40:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:40:01 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/105/1200x900,80/1622276/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://content.jwplatform.com/videos/Cu7GINqZ-r0yi2e87.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="62" height="1080" width="1920"><media:title><![CDATA[How to Make Cookie Dough Brownies]]></media:title><media:description><![CDATA[You know those indecisive baking moments when you absolutely cannot pick between making cookies or brownies? We have those moments often. So we figured the best thing to do was combine two of our favorite recipes. Do us a solid and try this cookie dough brownie that we have lovingly nicknamed the #brookie.]]></media:description><media:category>Food,Living,Recipe,So Sweet</media:category><media:thumbnail url="https://content.jwplatform.com/thumbs/Cu7GINqZ-720.jpg"/></media:content></item><item><title>The Best Way To Find Your True Voice Is To &quot;Om&quot;</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/throat-chakra-balance-exercise?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/throat-chakra-balance-exercise?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Bend It Like Beka <em>is a series designed to tune up your body with stretches that align your seven chakras — bringing balance and new energy into your life.</em></p><p>Improve your communication skills by working the throat chakra. Leave negativity and self-doubt behind to awaken your authentic self.</p><p>This video was created in partnership with <a href="http://www.drinksmartwater.com/#/home">smartwater</a>.</p><p>To see more, check out our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC09b9jzmuEUza8tuiaJtP8w">BRAWLERS</a> channel on YouTube.</p><script src="https://apis.google.com/js/platform.js"></script><div class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UC09b9jzmuEUza8tuiaJtP8w" data-layout="default" data-count="default"></div>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117179/suicide-rates-rising-young-women" title="Why Is Suicide On The Rise In Women?"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/045/x/1623118/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay" title="A Lesson In Imperfection"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2e9/x,80/1623167/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/what-is-an-orgasm" title="Here's What Happens To Your Body When You Have An Orgasm"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/913/x/1622230/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Lauren Perlstein.]]></media:credit></link><dc:creator>Laura Delarato</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:30:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 16:14:43 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/6b6/1200x900,80/1607585/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://content.jwplatform.com/videos/YUHREGmI-r0yi2e87.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="90" height="1080" width="1920"><media:title><![CDATA[The Best Way To Find Your True Voice Is To Ohm]]></media:title><media:description><![CDATA[Improve your communication skills by working the throat chakra. Leave negativity and self-doubt behind to awaken your authentic self.]]></media:description><media:category>Bend It Like Beka,Branded/Sponsored,Brawlers,Wellness</media:category><media:thumbnail url="https://content.jwplatform.com/thumbs/YUHREGmI-720.jpg"/></media:content></item><item><title>PSA: You Should Be Paying Way More Attention To Your Lips</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/lip-care-tips?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/lip-care-tips?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Because you're well-versed in the importance of taking care of your skin, your medicine cabinet is likely stocked with cleansers, serums, creams, sunscreens, and masks. But what if we told you there's one glaring feature on your face that you're probably not giving enough love to?</p><p>We're talking about your lips. They're there for you through all the eating, drinking, kissing, and <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/kylie-jenner-lip-kit-dupe-best-sellers#slide">Lip Kit-testing</a> — and you can do better by them. We chatted with Annet King, senior director of global education and innovation for Dermalogica, about why the skin on your lips is different than the skin on, say, your cheeks, and how you can make your pout look its best.</p><p>"The skin on the lips is extra thin and sensitive," King says. "[Lips] don't have any hair or sebaceous glands, which assist in keeping the skin lubricated and protected. Their only source of moisturizer is your saliva; that's why they can easily become dry and chapped." What's more, they don't have any melanin, which is your body's natural way of protecting the skin from ultraviolet rays. "That's why [your lips] are at a higher risk of sunburn and skin cancer," King adds.</p><p>The marks of healthy lips are volume and hydration. "Think of your lips as a sponge: When exposed to moisture, they absorb water and plump up," King explains. "When dehydrated, they dry out and shrink."</p><p>But as you age, your lips will begin to show fine lines and wrinkles — usually at a faster rate than the rest of your face, since the skin is so thin. King stresses that smoking is a major culprit of early aging of the lips. "Beside the damage caused by the toxins in the smoke itself, smokers are more likely to develop lines around the mouth, because of the repeated use of the perioral muscles to hold the cigarette," she says. (Not only will quitting smoking make your pout prettier, it'll probably get a lot more action once your breath doesn't smell like an ashtray.)</p><p>But cigarettes aren't the only aging culprit. "The cumulative damage to the lips and the skin results from years of overexposure to the sun, cold air, drying lip products, and harsh weather," King says. "The negative effects of the environment frequently result in the drying, chapping, and cracking of the mouth." Improper care of lips can also lead to increased risk of inflammation, infection, and burning sensations.</p><p>The good news is that once you start taking care of your pout, you can reverse the signs of aging and trauma relatively quickly. King recommends applying a protective balm with nut butter or avocado oil before leaving the house — these two ingredients are extremely nourishing. Also, don't forget to apply an SPF to guard against sun damage (we love <a href="http://www.sephora.com/sugar-sport-treatment-sunscreen-spf-30-P406676?skuId=1788363&icid2=products%20grid:p406676">this Fresh one</a>). But it goes further than that: "Exfoliate lips with <a href="http://www.lushusa.com/Mint-Julips/03057,en_US,pd.html">a gentle exfoliant</a> and follow with <a href="http://www.sephora.com/agave-lip-mask-P384629?skuId=1575042&om_mmc=ppc-GG&mkwid=sya8MM0SD&pcrid=102169856199&pdv=c&site=_search&country_switch=&lang=en&gclid=CM-7lvaG9s0CFYskhgod9WYEVQ">a hydrating mask</a> to combat roughness and cracking," King advises. But keep the exfoliation to once a week and make sure to avoid scrubs with salicylic aid. "It can erode through the lips' outer stratum corneum and damage living skin layers beneath."</p><p>If the damage is severe — for instance, if you're suffering from extreme dryness or sores — make sure to check in with a professional. They have a host of prescription products that can soothe your lips better than regular balm can.</p><p>"And stop licking your lips!" King says. "Licking your lips can contribute significantly to dry, cracked skin. The saliva evaporates quickly, taking with it any moisture that was already on them, leaving them even drier." (This is especially true in the winter.)</p><p>Now, go <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/lipstick-trends-2016">treat yourself to a lipstick</a>. You deserve it.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/face-primer-tips" title="Exactly How To Use Your Face Primer "><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/a8f/x,80/1377503/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:title><![CDATA[Primers_option2_MalloryHeyer]]></media:title></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/hormonal-acne-skin-care-regimen" title="Why Your Skin-Care Routine Should Change During Your Period"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/4d0/x/1622263/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/spa-treatments-blood-types" title="Blood Spas Are The Hot New Beauty Treatment"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/43b/x,80/1622871/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Maria Del Russo</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 22:03:16 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/428/1200x900,80/1621740/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>8 Things You Need To Know This AM</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/117050?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/117050?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/2ca/1200x900/1571835/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure><p><h3>1. Just Wrong: The brother of slain Pakistani model Qandeel Baloch confessed to killing her for "family honor."</h3></p><p>Waseem Azeem was arrested by police on Sunday and then presented to the media. He told The Associated Press that he killed his sister after being taunted about her photos on social media. "I was determined either to kill myself or kill her," he said. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117017/pakistani-model-death-honor-kiling">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>2. World News: At least 6,000 people in Turkey were detained in a government crackdown after Friday's failed coup attempt.</h3></p><p>Justice Minister Bekir Bozdağ told press in a television interview that "the cleansing (operation) is continuing. Some 6,000 detentions have taken place. The number could surpass 6,000." According to <a href="http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-36818401">The BBC</a>, the 6,000 detainees include high-ranking soldiers and over 2,000 judges. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116991/turkey-military-coup-attempt">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>3. Here At Home: Officials confirmed the identity of the suspected shooter in yesterday's deadly ambush against police.</h3></p><p>An official released the identity of the suspected shooter in Sunday's ambush on police in Baton Rouge, LA. The suspect was killed at the scene. The official spoke on condition of anonymity, due to the ongoing police investigation. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117030/baton-rouge-police-shooting">Read More</a>)</p><figure><img src="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/36d/1200x900,80/1622437/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900"/><figcaption><span class="copyright">Photo: Gerald Herbert/AP Images.</span></figcaption></figure><p><h3>4. In-The-Know: French police detained two new people in the investigation into Thursday's deadly attack in Nice.</h3></p><p>A French official confirmed that authorities had detained a man and woman. The official provided no details on their identities. Meanwhile, the estranged wife of truck driver Mohamed Lahouaiej Bouhlel was released from police custody. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116884/nice-france-truck-bastille-day">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>5. Talking Points: The Cleveland Police Union wants the Ohio governor to ban the open carrying of weapons during the Republican convention.</h3></p><p>The request from Cleveland Police Union President Steve Loomis follows the fatal shooting in Baton Rouge, LA, which left three police officers dead and three others wounded. Tens of thousands of protesters are expected to demonstrate outside the GOP convention. (<a href="http://time.com/4409725/cleveland-police-union-rnc-open-carry-2/?xid=homepage"><em>Time</em></a>)</p><p><h3>6. Don't Panic, But: According to the CDC, gonorrhea is developing a resistance to the drugs that are used to cure it.</h3></p><p>The CDC has found that there is an increasing number gonorrhea cases that have become resistant to the two drugs which are used in combination to treat the STD, azithromycin and ceftriaxone. The rise is small, but scientists say it is a warning of what could happen. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117045/gonorrhea-resistant-antibiotics">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>7. Real Talk: People who bit their nails and sucked their thumbs as children may have fewer allergies as adults, says a study.</h3></p><p>Researchers studied a pool of 1,037 children in New Zealand, tracking their nail-biting and thumb-sucking habits from the age of 5 to 11. Once the children reached their teen years, the researchers began testing them for common allergies, including dust mites, grass, cats, and dogs. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116874/biting-nails-immune-system-benefits">Read More</a>)</p><p><h3>8. Icebreaker: The most-used emoji on Tinder is the blushing smiley face.</h3></p><p>Another surprise may be the fact that so many on Tinder are using the dancing lady to communicate with their potential matches. This would definitely complement the music-note emoji, however, which also lands on this list. (<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117041/emoji-tinder-most-popular">Read More</a>)</p><figure><img src="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2d3/1200x900/1571954/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117202/melania-trump-plagiarize-michelle-obama" title="Why Everyone Is Tweeting About Melania Trump's RNC Speech"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/687/x,80/1623275/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[PhotoChip Somodevilla/Getty Images. ]]></media:credit></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117094/melania-trump-speech-rnc-opening-night" title="Here's What Melania Trump Wants You To Know About Her Husband"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/863/x,80/1623271/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photo: Getty Images. ]]></media:credit></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116982/republican-national-convention-2016-photos-opening-day" title="GOP Women Share Their Views As RNC Officially Kicks Off — In Photos"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/0f0/x,80/1623222/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Us</dc:creator><publishedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 10:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:30:55 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/daf/1200x900,80/1619511/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How One San Francisco Woman Saves $1,500 A Month</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-san-francisco-biotech-budget?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary-san-francisco-biotech-budget?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><em>Welcome to</em><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary">Money Diaries</a> <em>,</em> <em>where we're tackling what might be the last taboo facing modern working women: money. We're asking millennial women how they spend their hard-earned money during a seven-day period — and we're tracking every last dollar. (Thanks,</em><a href="http://nymag.com/thecut/2015/09/man-deciding-whether-to-cheat.html">New York <em>mag</em></a> <em>, for the inspiration.)</em></p><p><em>Today, a San Franciscan in biotech saving $1,500 a month for a down payment.</em></p><figure><img src="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/c2a/1200x900,80/1622145/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900"/></figure><p><strong>Industry:</strong> Biotechnology, data analytics, and strategy. I am extremely lucky to work for a company that has great perks (transportation, subsidized food, cell phone, and a gym — although I don’t use it), not to mention good health care and benefits. My monthly spending would undoubtedly be significantly higher if I switched jobs. It also helps that my office is a big campus/office-park setting where there isn’t a lot of temptation to spend money on lunch.</p><p><strong>Age:</strong> 26</p><p><strong>Location:</strong> San Francisco</p><p><strong>Salary:</strong> $115,000 with $24K pre-tax bonus last year (bonus went straight into savings,minus a $150 celebratory dinner)</p><p><strong>Paycheck Amount (2x/month):</strong> $2,638, after taxes, healthcare, HSA account contributions, and maxing out my 401(k) deductions for the year. I consider my monthly take-home pay to be $5,000 and keep the extra $138 in my checking as a cushion.</p><p><strong>Number of roommates:</strong> 1 (my fiancé)</p><p><strong>Monthly Expenses</strong></p><p><strong>Rent:</strong> $1,675, my half. We live in decent, but by no means luxurious, one-bedroom apartment (i.e., no dishwasher, no garbage disposal, bathroom with atrocious '70s tile and colors, etc.)</p><p><strong>Loans:</strong> $0 (very fortunate to have gotten a scholarship and parents paid for room and board)</p><p><strong>Utilities:</strong> $40, internet. We actually do have cable, because my fiancé likes to watch baseball. If it were up to me, we would just have HBO GO, so he pays the TV portion.</p><p><strong>Cell Phone:</strong> $0, work pays for it. (I had the option of either getting a second iPhone just for work, or have work pay for my personal phone — clearly chose the latter).</p><p><strong>House Cleaning:</strong> $100 a month. We have a housekeeper come twice a month and she charges $100 for each visit, so we take turns paying.</p><p><strong>Netflix:</strong> $8</p><p><strong>Future Fun:</strong> $450. At the beginning of the year, I tallied up the costs of all the trips, travel, weddings, major gifts, and expenses I knew I had to pay for, and then divided that by 12 to understand what I should be “saving” each month. That way, the big expenses don’t skew the picture of what’s really going on every month and that I don’t overspend in months where I don’t have to buy a plane ticket or gift and feel more flush than usual. As for my own wedding, we are planning on having a small, low-key ceremony at city hall followed by dinner out. Our parents will be graciously picking up the tab for that.</p><p><strong>Transportation:</strong> $0 fixed. My company runs private shuttles from S.F. to our campus, located in South San Francisco near the airport. My fiancé also has a car (I contribute towards his car insurance, which is included in “Future Fun,” but usually not gas, unless we are taking a trip out of town).</p><p><strong>Monthly savings for down payment:</strong> $1,500. I’ve got about $45,000 in savings so far, but the median home price in the Bay Area is like $800K, so it feels like chump change at this point.</p><p><strong>Leftover discretionary money:</strong> ~$1,200</p><p><h3>Day One</h3> 8:45 a.m — I make tea at home (20 cents per bag) and bring a Fage 2% yogurt to eat at my desk ($1, on sale from Safeway). <strong>$1.20</strong></p><p>10:50 a.m. — I get hungry and swing by the office kitchen for an apple (we get a weekly fruit delivery on Monday that normally lasts until Wednesday or Thursday).</p><p>2:15 p.m. — Was too busy to stop and take a lunch break, so I eat some Mexican leftovers in the kitchen from an earlier meeting.</p><p>6 p.m. – Go for run in Golden Gate Park.</p><p>7 p.m. — Fiancé makes dinner: a layered salad of avocado, tomatoes, onion. We also make a flatbread out of half a ball of prepared pizza dough from Whole Foods (which are so good and only $1.29!) and eat it with some hummus. He pays for most of our dinner groceries and I pay for wine and booze. We are recovering from a boozy weekend, so no wine tonight. Catch up on HBO shows ( <em>Veep, Silicon Valley, GoT,</em> and John Oliver) and go to bed.</p><p><strong>Daily Total: $1.20</strong></p><p><h3>Day Two</h3> 8:45 a.m. — Tea (20 cents per bag) and Fage ($1). <strong>$1.20</strong></p><p>10:30 a.m — Grab another pear from the office fruit basket and also sneak a handful of peanut M&M's.</p><p>12:45 p.m. — Head over to the cafeteria, which is actually pretty decent (same food company as Google has); while not free, is subsidized, so the prices are pretty good. Get a large bowl of soup and some crackers. <strong>$2.56</strong></p><p>1:30 p.m. — Our office is freezing, so make myself a bland, but free, cup of tea.</p><p>5:10 p.m — Walking home from shuttle, stop at CVS for a Diet Snapple, box of granola bars, face wash, Ziploc bags, and hand soap: <strong>$22.32</strong></p><p>8 p.m. — Same dinner as last night, with the second half of the pizza dough as flatbread. Open up a bottle of red wine, $14. Prep for a big presentation tomorrow and go over my notes until bed. <strong>$14</strong></p><p><strong>Daily Total: $40.08</strong></p><p><h3>Day Three</h3> 8:45 a.m. — Same as other days, tea at home and yogurt at desk. <strong>$1.20</strong></p><p>12 p.m. — Meeting during lunch, which is always catered. Today is sandwich boxes from Boudin Bakery.</p><p>2:15 p.m. — My friend has posted online asking for donations to fund her city’s chapter of Big Brothers Big Sisters, so I donate: <strong>$50</strong></p><p>5:10 p.m. — Walking home from the shuttle and it’s gorgeous out. Stop for froyo, because I’m relieved my presentation went well and is over. <strong>$3.86</strong></p><p>5:20 p.m. — Stop at public library to pick up a book that has been put on hold for me.</p><p>6 p.m. — Go for run in Golden Gate Park.</p><p>7:30 p.m. — Fiance makes bucatini all’amatriciana, one of our favorite meals. We probably eat pasta once a week to keep costs down, as well as have something simple. I picked up a bottle of red to have with it. <strong>$11</strong></p><p><strong>Daily Total: $66.06</strong></p><p><h3>Day Four</h3> 8:45 a.m. — Tea and yogurt. <strong>$1.20</strong></p><p>12 p.m. — Go to office cafeteria for a BLT with avocado. <strong>$4.45</strong></p><p>12:30 p.m. — Craving something sweet, so stop by snack cabinet for three mini Reese's.</p><p>4 p.m. — Perusing Madewell’s website and see a cute top that’s on sale, <strong>$38</strong>. Apparently, I normally spend about $120 per month on clothes according to my spreadsheets.</p><p>7 p.m. — We meet some friends at a bar to celebrate our recent engagement. I have a cocktail and two glasses of wine, along with some bar snacks. They are sweet and pick up the tab and we UberPool home, <strong>$6.75.</strong></p><p><strong>Daily Total: $50.40</strong></p><p><h3>Day Five</h3></p><p>9 a.m. — Between the drinks last night and not eating a full dinner, I’m feeling not-so-hot and treat myself to a cappuccino and at the fancy office coffee bar. I also eat one of the granola bars I bought from CVS the other day. <strong>$2.85.</strong></p><p>1 p.m. — Office cafeteria chana masala and rice. <strong>$4.15</strong></p><p>2:45 p.m. — Read an article about Trump being more racist and misogynistic than normal, am prompted donate to HRC. <strong>$10</strong></p><p>7 p.m. — We invite friends over for dinner and end up ordering pizza for everyone, since no one wants to cook. Everyone else brings wine, so no money spent on booze. I split the cost with my fiancé, so I pay <strong>$29.</strong></p><p>10:15 p.m. — Some folks leave and want to go to a bar for another drink, but I’m feeling tired from last night and the week, so I crawl into bed, instead.</p><p><strong>Daily Total: $46</strong></p><p><h3>Day Six</h3></p><p>9:30 a.m. — Go out for bagels and coffee. <strong>$9</strong></p><p>11 a.m. — Stop at Nordstrom Rack to get a new bra and manage to get out of there without buying anything else. <strong>$18.45</strong></p><p>1 p.m. — Burrito and a Diet Coke from a taco truck for lunch, fiancé pays.</p><p>3 p.m. — We ended up walking all the way to Ocean Beach, because it’s sunny and warm out, but are too tired to walk the six-and-a-half miles home, so I call an Uber, <strong>$9</strong></p><p>4 p.m. — Book a rental car for a wedding we are going to in Hawaii in September, but it’s already been planned for in the “Future Fun” budget. <strong>$48</strong></p><p>7 p.m. — Eat leftover pizza for dinner, along with a salad fiancé made to supplement, and start watching <em>OITNB</em> season 4. We split a bottle of wine and have a quiet night in. <strong>$12.</strong></p><p><strong>Daily Total: $96.45</strong></p><p><h3>Day Seven</h3> 9 a.m. — Peanut-butter toast and coffee at home for breakfast.</p><p>11 a.m. — Go for a run and stop at a deli on the way back to pick up sandwiches and chips for myself and fiancé for lunch. <strong>$17.56</strong></p><p>2:15 p.m. — Do laundry and nap. We have laundry in our basement, which is not coin-operated — huge perk!</p><p>3:30 p.m. — Walk to Whole Foods and buy a few things for the upcoming week, such as avocados, cheese, crackers, etc. <strong>$16.82</strong></p><p>6 p.m. — Fiance’s family lives in the Bay Area, so we head down to Palo Alto for dinner at a steakhouse. We probably have family dinner two to three Sundays a month. His dad graciously pays for everyone.</p><p><strong>Daily Total: $34.38</strong></p><figure><img src="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/0e7/1200x900/1622141/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/></figure><p><em>Money Diaries are meant to reflect individual women’s experiences and do not necessarily reflect Refinery29’s point of view. Refinery29 in no way encourages illegal activity or harmful behavior.</em></p><p><em>The first step to getting your financial life in order is tracking what you spend — to try on your own, check out <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/budgeting-tools-spending-diary">our guide to managing your money every day</a>. For more money diaries, click<a href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diary">here</a>.</em></p><p><em>Have a money diary you'd like to share? Email <a href="mailto:moneydiary@refinery29.com">moneydiary@refinery29.com</a>.</em></p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117171/paying-cash-benefits-research" title="Paying In Cash Hurts So Good, According To Research"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/89b/x,80/1622970/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/money-diaries-saving-advice" title="8 Quotes That Show What Millennial Women Really Think About Money"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/5f2/x/1622751/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117112/rich-kid-trust-fund-personal-essay" title="I'm The Trust Fund Baby You Love To Hate"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/ae1/x,80/1622603/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Us</dc:creator><publishedDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 21:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 18:08:34 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/818/1200x900/1622143/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>5 Hacks For A Healthier Week</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/kayla-itsines-circuit-workout?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/kayla-itsines-circuit-workout?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Got 15 minutes? Then you have more than enough time to try celebrity trainer <a href="http://pubx.ch/29VQ6eD">Kayla Itsine's go-to circuit workout</a>.</p><p>If you've been struggling to fall asleep during these warmer months, you might be overlooking one of the <a href="http://www.wellandgood.com/good-advice/sleeping-naked-benefits/">simplest sleep hacks</a> out there.</p><p>Did you know you can <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/dehydration#slide-5">eat your water</a>? Here are <a href="http://www.prevention.com/food/8-tasty-foods-that-help-you-rehydrate-naturally/slide/1">eight foods that will help you rehydrate</a>.</p><p>Hopefully, you took a well-deserved break from your workout routine while on vacation. Getting back to it doesn't have to be daunting — here are <a href="http://elitedaily.com/wellness/steps-working-out-avoiding-gym/1543125/?utm_source=elitedaily&utm_medium=syndication&utm_campaign=wgelitedaily">five ways</a> to get back into the exercise groove.</p><p>And finally, whether you're a fan of jogging, cycling, or dancing, here are <a href="http://www.self.com/food/2016/07/the-best-snacks-to-eat-after-a-cardio-workout/">the best snacks to eat</a> after a cardio session.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117179/suicide-rates-rising-young-women" title="Why Is Suicide On The Rise In Women?"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/045/x/1623118/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay" title="A Lesson In Imperfection"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2e9/x,80/1623167/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/what-is-an-orgasm" title="Here's What Happens To Your Body When You Have An Orgasm"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/913/x/1622230/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Lauren Perlstein.]]></media:credit></link><dc:creator>Sara Coughlin</dc:creator><publishedDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 22:19:25 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/491/1200x900,80/1622155/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Blood Spas Are The Hot New Beauty Treatment</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/spa-treatments-blood-types?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/spa-treatments-blood-types?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>When you think of a relaxing day at the spa, your mind generally conjures up images of someone massaging every last knot out of your shoulders or layering on a mud mask. What doesn’t usually come to mind is having your blood drawn — a procedure typically reserved for the doctor’s office.</p><p>But if you happen to live like one of the <a href="https://www.instagram.com/richkidsofinstagram/?hl=en">#RichKidsOfInstagram</a> — jet-setting about for lavish long weekends (or you’re a globe-trotter and simply understand the finer things in life) — you might have noticed that some of the higher end spas have become extremely interested in your medical history in recent years.</p><p>Many of the top spas around the world are investing in medical services in order to deliver wellness practices to correct what ails you — whether it’s related to weight loss, energy loss, your immune system, your digestive system, or simply stress.</p><p>In order to achieve this, they're working with their patients on getting blood samples prior to their spa stays to make sure they're offered just the right treatments. Of course, we had to learn more about this crazy trend. We spoke with multiple spas about this newfound blood thirst — and even lent a vein — in the name of research.</p><p><strong>Your Blood Horoscope</strong></p><p>At <a href="http://www.albereta.it/en/spa-espace-chenot">Espace Chenot</a> at L’Albereta — a health and wellness spa picturesquely situated in a vineyard in a small wine region of Northern Italy called Franciacorta — Dr. Elena Rossetti, the in-house doctor, told us that the staff works to pair their medical knowledge with appropriate treatments for each patient. That's where the blood tests come in. "Based on the results of the blood tests and anti-aging tests, the doctor proposes a personalized process."</p><figure><img src="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/eb5/1200x900/1620512/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/><figcaption><span class="copyright">Illustrated by Elliot Salazar.</span></figcaption></figure><p>We had the opportunity to try out <a href="http://www.albereta.it/en/spa-espace-chenot/treatments/medical">Ozone Therapy</a> — one of the spa's star treatments — during a recent trip to Franciacorta. The treatment is given to patients multiple times a week during their stay to, purportedly, boost the metabolism, help the immune system, improve memory, and assist with weight loss.</p><p>Dr. Rossetti explained that during Ozone Therapy, 100ml of your blood is drawn, mixed with oxygen, and then basically put back in your body. “The oxygen is nutrition for the cells, so it helps them to grow,” says Dr. Rossetti.</p><p>If we were patients at the spa (and staying the normal two weeks suggested), she would recommend this treatment up to 10 times during the stay in order to truly get the most out of it, and then to return once a month for maintenance. Considering each treatment costs about $170 a pop, this is pretty much a 1%-only type of deal.</p><p><strong>Testing, Testing...</strong></p><p>The doctors measure the therapy's effectiveness by conducting more blood tests throughout the treatment and at the conclusion, testing for things like cholesterol and glucose levels.</p><p>As for the procedure itself, it took all of 15 minutes. Blood doesn't make us queasy, but this is definitely not for the faint of heart. Being hooked up to a machine and seeing so much blood taken out (and mixed in a glass bottle hanging above our head) was a little unnerving. Our first thought was along the lines of: <em>What the hell? I want my blood back...</em> Thankfully after mere minutes, the entire 100ml of blood was back where it belonged and we were on our way.</p><blockquote>Our first thought was along the lines of: 'What the hell? I want my blood back...'</blockquote><p>After Ozone Therapy, it was time for a massage, which Sara Suardi, the spa director, informed us was to go hand-in-hand with the treatment. The Chinese massage technique is said to help boost metabolism and purge the body of the mental and environmental aggressors that can show up on your skin.</p><p>We thought the blood part was going to be the weirdest, but the massage was one of the strangest and most intricate ones we've ever had — and being in the beauty business, we’ve experienced hundreds.</p><p>The therapist concentrated her efforts along the spine with a vibrating stone, and then she went to work hand-massaging the stomach for about 20 minutes.</p><p>Massaging the stomach and digestive organs is said to be good for your digestion, but it is also very uncomfortable if you feel like you've been eating a lot for the past few days. But that discomfort did lead to some positive results — typically, traveling can cause a little bit of, um, blockage, and this massage worked out any evacuation (read: poop) issues. So, whatever her magical hands did, it worked.</p><p>For a lengthier stay, a guest would receive multiple treatments like this throughout the week. But even after our one treatment, we noticed some great results: Immediately after, we didn't struggle at all with jet lag or feel run-down, and we were nonstop touring a new country, which can be pretty exhausting.</p><p><strong>Mail-Order Blood</strong></p><p>In Saint Lucia, The <a href="https://www.thebodyholiday.com/">BodyHoliday</a> has also been doing medical analysis to recommend appropriate treatments. But instead of going through rigorous rounds of testing when they first arrive, guests receive a series of online questionnaires. The spa sends them a lab-test kit with step-by-step instructions in the mail. The kit might even ask for a stool sample (depending on the guest’s needs). Side note: This might be the only situation in which sending poop in the mail is considered acceptable. Although we'd hate to be the post-office employee who has to handle that particular package.</p><p>On arrival, guests go through a non-invasive test (i.e. no blood removed from your body and swished around in a jar over your head) to analyze more than 130 blood parameters. Those are grouped with the results from the test kit for a complete pre-treatment health profile.</p><p>The BodyHoliday’s Wellness Centre leader Dr. Arun Pillai tells us that the aim of this kind of treatment is “to take people to a place of more efficient cellular and improved metabolic function, and a better immune function." This is done through a combination of specialized treatments, healthy food, and "advanced nutritional supplements specifically aimed at correcting any measured imbalances.”</p><figure><img src="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/728/1200x900/1620511/image.png" width="1200" height="900"/><figcaption><span class="copyright">Illustrated by Elliot Salazar.</span></figcaption></figure><p>Dr. Pillai says that, unlike many other spa treatments, this practice is rooted in functional science.</p><p>“This is purely based on medical science. The goal of the examinations is to determine changes in composition of...chemical reactions shaped by the blood...that have interconnections with oxygen consumption and carbon-dioxide exhaust regulated by organisms [that] have influenced the level of protein and lipids in cell membranes,” Dr. Pillai tells us.</p><p><strong>Finding Balance</strong></p><p>Other well-known (and celebrity-frequented) spas — like <a href="http://www.canyonranchdestinations.com/">Canyon Ranch</a> — have been using medical science to assist with wellness treatments for years, but do not (as of yet) use any blood tests to determine treatments. Instead, according to Canyon Ranch's medical director, Stephen Brewer, MD, physicians help direct their guests toward a healthy-living plan throughout their stay.</p><p>Only time will tell whether more spas will use medically directed approaches in the future. But since the majority focus on beauty and relaxation, rather than diagnosing health issues, this isn't something we see becoming the norm anytime soon. Yet, as Dr. Pillai so accurately points out, a blood test can speak volumes — and if we have to spill a little blood in order to whip our immune systems into shape, so be it.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/face-primer-tips" title="Exactly How To Use Your Face Primer "><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/a8f/x,80/1377503/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/><media:title><![CDATA[Primers_option2_MalloryHeyer]]></media:title></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/hormonal-acne-skin-care-regimen" title="Why Your Skin-Care Routine Should Change During Your Period"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/4d0/x/1622263/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/lip-care-tips" title="PSA: You Should Be Paying Way More Attention To Your Lips"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/f5e/x,80/1621740/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Rachel Adler</dc:creator><publishedDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 18:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 18:46:32 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/191/1200x900,80/1622871/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Split Squats Are Your Quads' New Best Friend </title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/split-quat-leg-workout-move?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/split-quat-leg-workout-move?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>60 Seconds To Fit <em>is a quick and easy way to ignite a new workout routine or give yours a fresh upgrade.</em></p><p>Split squats are no joke. They work your lower body while improving your balance — all on one foot! Give it a go on the nearest park bench.</p><p>This video was created in partnership with <a href="http://www.drinksmartwater.com/#/home">smartwater</a>.</p><p>To see more, check out our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC09b9jzmuEUza8tuiaJtP8w">BRAWLERS</a> channel on YouTube.</p><script src="https://apis.google.com/js/platform.js"></script><div class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UC09b9jzmuEUza8tuiaJtP8w" data-layout="default" data-count="default"></div>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117179/suicide-rates-rising-young-women" title="Why Is Suicide On The Rise In Women?"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/045/x/1623118/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay" title="A Lesson In Imperfection"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2e9/x,80/1623167/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/what-is-an-orgasm" title="Here's What Happens To Your Body When You Have An Orgasm"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/913/x/1622230/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Lauren Perlstein.]]></media:credit></link><dc:creator>Laura Delarato</dc:creator><dc:creator>Vacation</dc:creator><dc:creator>EXECUTIVE PRODUCED by Rafael Jimenez</dc:creator><dc:creator>PRODUCED by Jiro Kohl</dc:creator><dc:creator>ASSOCIATE PRODUCED by Kevin Kushner</dc:creator><dc:creator>Directed by Nick Ray McCann</dc:creator><dc:creator>Styled By by Laura Pritchard</dc:creator><dc:creator>HAIR + MAKEUP by Marina Guidos</dc:creator><dc:creator>Set Design by Lizzie Lang</dc:creator><dc:creator>Bra by Rebecca Minkoff</dc:creator><dc:creator>Pant by H&amp;amp;M</dc:creator><dc:creator>Shoe by Adidas by Stella McCartney, available at &amp;nbsp;Bandier&amp;nbsp;</dc:creator><publishedDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 14:30:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 20:40:08 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/b1b/1200x900,80/1620825/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://content.jwplatform.com/videos/F0jfNZzv-r0yi2e87.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="47" height="1080" width="1920"><media:title><![CDATA[Split Squats Are Your Quads New Best Friend]]></media:title><media:description><![CDATA[Split squats are no joke. They work your lower body while improving your balancing — all on one foot! Give it a go on the nearest park bench.]]></media:description><media:category>60 Seconds To Fit,Branded/Sponsored,Brawlers,Wellness</media:category><media:thumbnail url="https://content.jwplatform.com/thumbs/F0jfNZzv-720.jpg"/></media:content></item><item><title>How To Grow Your Beauty Following On Instagram</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/get-more-instagram-followers-beauty-hashtags?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/get-more-instagram-followers-beauty-hashtags?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>How many times a day do you check Instagram? Is the number in the double digits? If you answered a resounding "yes," you are not alone. Throughout the day, I check the app too many times to count — when I wake up, before I go to sleep, on the subway, heck, I even check it in the bathroom (TMI, sorry). Clearly, I'm addicted — and I'm guessing you are, too.</p><p>But perusing Instagram and creating your own community on it are two different things, and it takes some dedication to boost a beauty following. After all, a <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/instagram-flat-lay-photography#slide">pixelated flat lay</a> does not an A+ feed make. That's why we decided to tap two Insta-experts: beauty YouTuber Manny Gutierrez (he goes by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/BH0-zyQhg3z/?taken-by=mannymua733&hl=en">@mannymua733</a> and has 2.1 million followers) and blogger and businesswoman, Laura Gurrola (her Insta handle is <a href="https://www.instagram.com/laurag_143/?hl=en">@lauraag_143</a> and she clocks in at 2 million followers). Below, they share their tips on how to grow your beauty following on the app. Check 'em out, below.</p><iframe allowtransparency="true" src="https://instagram.com/p/BH0-zyQhg3z/" frameborder="0"/><p><strong>Quality Counts</strong></p><p>Gurrola and Gutierrez both agree that photo quality can make or break your page. “If someone posts a photo that’s really blurry and dark, you can barely see the makeup,” says Gutierrez. But don’t run out and buy hundreds of dollars worth of expensive equipment just yet.</p><p>According to Gutierrez, all you need is <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/instagram-flat-lay-photography">daylight and a phone</a> (he often uses his iPhone). “Daylight is the best lighting you can have,” he says. “There are plenty of camera phones that are amazing [quality]. Go outside, take selfies, do what you have to do. Use the resources you have to propel your career.” And if you're shooting inside, try to take photos facing a window to get that natural light.</p><figure><img src="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/804/1200x900,80/1621785/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900"/></figure><p><strong>Know The Power Of Hashtags</strong></p><p>Gurrola and Gutierrez insist that hashtags are the best way to get new eyes on your work. "Instagram allows you to use 30 hashtags, use every single one of them," Gurrola advises. "People really do look at hashtags, so more people will be able to see your work."</p><p>Hashtags like #HudaBeauty, #WakeupAndMakeup, and Gurrola's own #Lauraag143 are good places to start. All three of these hashtags were created by women who run their own Instagram-aggregation pages. If one of these women like what they see on their hashtags, they might repost your image to their millions of followers.</p><p>Gurrola also suggests searching for popular beauty hashtags and making use of the "related hashtags" section at the top of the screen to discover more. Some hashtags that she uses are #makeupoftheday and #beauty. "If [you find it] embarrassing to put hashtags in your caption, put it in a comment, because by the time you have three comments it will be hidden," Gurrola adds.</p><iframe allowtransparency="true" src="https://instagram.com/p/BET1meVPwSg/" frameborder="0"/><p><strong>Consistency Is Key</strong></p><p>"If you're going to go into social media, you can't be half-assed [about it]," says Guiterrez. "You need to invest yourself in a way." That's why both social-media mavens strongly urge anyone looking to grow their following to post consistently — at least once or twice a day, according to Guitterez.</p><p>Timing is also important when it comes to Instagram. When Gurrola was starting out, she kept a journal where she recorded her engagement (likes and comments) to see what times worked best for her page. There are even apps, like <a href="http://whentogram.com/">When To Gram</a>, that help analyze when your followers will most likely be on the app. "Super-early morning or evening works best for me," she says. "You have to find the times that work [for you]; it's not going to happen overnight, but be consistent and post once a day to keep your page active."</p><p><strong>You Do You</strong></p><p>As cliché as it may sound, at the end of the day, the best advice Gurrola and Guiterrez can give is to always post content that's true to <em>you.</em> They stress the importance of being yourself and finding your passion — the rest will follow. If you love lips and shoes, post your favorite liquid lipsticks and heels. Remember, there are thousands of people out there who share your interests. They might just be a hashtag away.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/04/109151/kim-kardashian-makeup" title="You Have To See How Much Kim Kardashian Has Changed"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/861/x,80/1582293/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117166/kat-von-d-vault-collection-teaser" title="Kat Von D Teases Some Next-Level Beauty Launches"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/179/x,80/1623007/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117156/shay-mitchell-red-hair" title="Shay Mitchell Test-Drives A New Hair Color — &amp;amp; It's Her Best Yet"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/614/x/1622926/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Mi-Anne Chan </dc:creator><publishedDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 14:00:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 22:10:16 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/8fc/1200x900,80/1621778/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Erin Yamagata.]]></media:credit></media:content></item><item><title>Here's How Your Menstrual Cycle Affects Your Workouts</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/exercise-during-period-workout-effects?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/exercise-during-period-workout-effects?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>When we think of our menstrual cycles, we tend to think only of the <em>exceedingly fun</em> week of our period. But that ebb and flow of hormones can affect many parts of your life throughout the month — including our workouts.</p><p>Some days, it may feel a little like you're in one of those awful math problems about a snail — one step forward and two steps back. For example, maybe last week you ran faster than you've ever been able to; this week, you can barely get through a mile, leaving you feeling frustrated. The important thing to remember? "It's your physiology, not your fitness [level]," says Stacy Sims, PhD, an environmental exercise physiologist at the <a href="http://www.uowadamshpc.co.nz/page/sports-science/">University of Waikato</a> in New Zealand. In fact, the normal hormonal changes your body goes through can affect everything from your energy levels to how much hydration you need after a hard workout — depending on where you are in your cycle.</p><p>Here's a stage-by-stage breakdown of what's happening — and what you can do to make these changes more managable.</p><p><strong>Post-Period</strong></p><p>In the early days of this stage, both estrogen and progesterone levels are low. At this point, Dr. Sims says to "go for it!" and push hard, as this will be the part of the month where you feel strongest. You could even go as far as trying to schedule your biggest challenges (a long run or a hard hike) during these days. It's a small window, though, so it may not always be possible to do this. Once estrogen begins to creep upwards again as you head towards ovulation, you may begin to feel more fatigued, she says.</p><p><strong>Ovulation</strong></p><p>The few days before and during ovulation are when estrogen levels peak and then quickly decrease. In addition to needing a little extra sleep, some research suggests women may be especially prone to injury from here through the PMS phase.</p><p>In particular, studies have shown that before puberty, boys and girls tend to get ACL injuries at about the same rate. Once puberty hits, however, girls are about <a href="http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1318512/">twice as likely</a> as boys to have those injuries. Other studies have shown that women who take hormonal birth control (and therefore don't experience the hormonal ups and downs of a normal menstural cycle) <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/03/106494/birth-control-prevents-knee-injury-estrogen">have lower rates of ACL injuries</a> than those who don't. So, researchers think our <a href="http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22784194">hormones may have a role to play</a> here. These hormonal changes may increase reaction time slightly and make you feel a bit foggier, Dr. Sims says.</p><p>This doesn't mean you need to skip your favorite indoor cycling or bootcamp class during ovulation or anything. Instead, it's just something to keep in mind. "Take it easy this day," Dr. Sims says.</p><p><strong>Premenstrual</strong></p><p>Even if your PMS tends to be relatively mild, this is when shit can get <em>real</em> for your willingness to work out <em>:</em> Progesterone begins to increase at this point and estrogen (after the drop that occurs right after ovulation) also begins to increase again around this time. The result: you might feel like you've "lost your mojo," says Dr. Sims, because these hormones can lead to fatigue.</p><p>Plus, progesterone can have catabolic effects, meaning that it encourages the breaking down of muscle proteins, Dr. Sims explains. It also increases the amount of sodium you excrete. So, your workouts may feel more difficult and recovering from them might take a little longer, too.</p><p>"After a hard, intense workout, the need for protein and hydration (fluid with sodium) is increased in times of elevated progesterone," Dr. Sims says. On top of that, progesterone is known to be thermogenic, meaning it can heat up your core temperature.</p><p>To combat all of that, Dr. Sims suggests drinking cold beverages before and during your gym session and adding a bit of salt to your food. She also recommends eating 25 grams of protein with a high leucine content (e.g., chicken, fish, and legumes) within a half hour of finishing your workout.</p><p><strong>Your Period</strong></p><p>During your period, estrogen and progesterone levels are at their lowest, which makes it easier for your body to access glycogen as a source of energy, rather than relying on the slower break down of fatty acids, Dr. Sims explains. So, you might find that you're hitting higher intensities faster during your workouts when on your period.</p><p>However, everyone's cycle is unique in fun (or not so fun) ways. Plus, your fitness level matters a lot, too. While it's important to stay active, it's also crucial to pay attention to the full picture — including taking rest days when needed, eating a balanced diet, and <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/03/105706/menstrual-cycle-sleep">getting enough sleep</a> — all month long.</p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay" title="A Lesson In Imperfection"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2e9/x,80/1623167/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116843/joy-bryant-beautiful-model-personal-story" title="Girl, You Beautiful"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/20e/x/1621684/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117045/gonorrhea-resistant-antibiotics" title="Gonorrhea May Soon Be Untreatable "><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/3dc/x/1622424/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Sarah Jacoby</dc:creator><publishedDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 21:20:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 21:23:34 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/604/1200x900,80/1621788/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"><media:credit><![CDATA[Photographed by Jens Ingvarsson. ]]></media:credit></media:content></item><item><title>9 Stories That Truly Capture What The Journey To Body Positivity Is Like</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/9-stories-of-body-positivity?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/9-stories-of-body-positivity?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>If you regularly read our work, you probably already know that, here at Refinery29, we are all about body positivity. In fact, we launched our <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/take-back-the-beach">Take Back the Beach</a> initiative to show that <em>every</em> body is a beach body, and to reframe the way people think and talk about body image and self-acceptance.</p><p>However, we also know that a positive body image is a journey, and that journey is not a linear one. Here, we've rounded up nine stories that show the various paths toward body positivity. Read, get inspired, and get ready to take back the beach.</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/elna-baker-weight-loss-surgery-loose-skin"><strong>What Losing 110 Pounds REALLY Looks Like</strong></a></p><p>"I don't know about you, but I am so sick of striving for fucking beauty. It has taken up 10 to 20% of my time and thoughts on a daily basis for the past 20 years. It has robbed me of doing more important, loving, honest things. And, after all this time, I'm not even that good at it."</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/top-transgender-surgery-photos#slide-1"><strong>How Going From A Woman To A White Man Changed My Perspective (NSFW)</strong></a></p><p>"The biggest challenges in this transition are dealing with the outside world, dealing with how people see me now. I was dealing with that before, but people saw me as, like, a dyke, a lesbian, or a really masculine woman. And they have their ideas about it, and I don’t care, but it's interesting to me going from that and being viewed as a woman and then being viewed as a man."</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/06/115111/stephanie-march-breast-augmentation-story"><strong>Why I Got Breast Implants — & Then Had Them Removed</strong></a></p><p>"But finally, once and for all, this isn’t about what anyone else thinks. It really does not matter anymore. I have accepted this episode as a part of my larger story. And I refuse to be ashamed of it. I am taking back my body, my story, and myself in a bathing suit. Today, the scars are fading into fine white lines. My breasts are small, well proportioned, and just right for my body. "</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/people-with-disabilities-beach-pictures#slide"><strong>9 Stunning Photos Of Differently Abled Women Taking Back The Beach</strong></a></p><p>"Women who have disabilities can be anything from army lieutenants and Broadway performers to track-and-field stars and leading scientists — and they sure as hell can enjoy beaches and pools."</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/04/109382/lemonade-black-body-beauty"><strong>How <em>Lemonade</em> Is Teaching Me To Love My Black Body</strong></a></p><p>"Beyoncé’s triumph in <em>Lemonade</em> is that through her personal struggle, she turns the mirror on us. I recognize my doubts in hers, hear my weaknesses in her voice, see myself in the eyes of the Black women who fill this album till it runneth over. Every Black woman is different, but Beyoncé has tapped into something we all experience: the fear that we are not enough in a world that doesn’t wish to see us, our battle to self-love, or our incredible capacity to feel, yet endure. When we are hurt, we are denied our humanity; when we succeed, our femininity."</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/body-image-curvy-southern-women"><strong>How Living In The South Fixed My Body Image</strong></a></p><p>"Indian people — at least the ones I know and know of — have a tendency to feed and feed you until you lay incapacitated on a couch. It’s a part of our culture of hospitality. But at the same time, if you’re a woman, heaven help you if you gain too much weight from this incessant food-pushing. Generally, in my culture, women get 'fat,' while men get 'healthy' and 'look good.'"</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/05/110996/self-love-acceptance-struggle-weight"><strong>The Truth About Accepting Your Body As-Is</strong></a></p><p>"But body acceptance is exactly <em>for</em> people 'like me' — because it’s for everyone. Because it’s never just about accepting your appearance and your weight. It’s about <em>self</em> -acceptance — the entire self, not just the visible bits. It’s challenging the idea that your exterior is indicative of your value as a human being."</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/fatkini-plus-size-bikini-body-positivity"><strong>My Body Is Not Safe For Work</strong></a></p><p>"Can you see my stomach?"</p><p>"I mean, yeah?"</p><p>"Good! I just don't want to look like I'm hiding anything."</p><p><a href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/115304/plus-size-female-athlete-louise-green"><strong>Fighting To Be Seen As A Plus-Size Athlete</strong></a></p><p>"Until fitness media and advertising dare to show these bodies, it’s up to you and I. Being seen as a plus-size athlete isn’t just about inspiring people of size. It’s also about showing society that body diversity exists in athleticism. It broadens the scope of what it means to be an athlete. What we see at those finish lines changes our very concept of the athletic ideal."</p><p><em>It's your body. It's your summer. Enjoy them both. <a href="http://www.refinery29.com/take-back-the-beach">Check out more #TakeBackTheBeach here</a>.</em></p>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/ronda-rousey-perfect-never-confidence-essay" title="A Lesson In Imperfection"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/2e9/x,80/1623167/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/116843/joy-bryant-beautiful-model-personal-story" title="Girl, You Beautiful"><media:thumbnail url="http://s2.r29static.com//bin/entry/20e/x/1621684/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117045/gonorrhea-resistant-antibiotics" title="Gonorrhea May Soon Be Untreatable "><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/3dc/x/1622424/image.png" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Kimberly Truong</dc:creator><publishedDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 18:40:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 20:02:30 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/231/1200x900/1622160/image.png" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Make Chocolate Strawberry Shots</title><link>http://www.refinery29.com/chocolate-strawberry-shot-recipe-video?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</link><guid>http://www.refinery29.com/chocolate-strawberry-shot-recipe-video?utm_source=newscred&amp;utm_medium=rss</guid><description><![CDATA[<style type="text/css">
.schemaRecipeContainer{
font:12px Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;
}
.schemaRecipeContainer a{
color:#000;
}
.schemaRecipeName,
.schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader,
.schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformationFacts{
font-weight:bold;
font-size:16px;
display:block;
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader,
.schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader{
padding-top:10px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions{}
.schemaRecipeAuthor{
font-weight:bold;
}
.schemaRecipeDatePublished{
padding-left:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeDescription,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformation{
display:block;
padding:10px 0;
}
.schemaRecipePrepTime,
.schemaRecipeCookTime,
.schemaRecipeYield,
.schemaRecipeNutritionInformation span{
display:block;
}
.schemaRecipeIngredients{
padding:0 0 0 18px;
margin:0;
}
.schemaRecipeIngredients li{
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions ol{
padding:0 0 0 18px;
margin:0;
}
.schemaRecipeInstructions li{
padding-bottom:5px;
}
.schemaRecipeCredits{
padding-top:10px;
}
</style><div itemscope="" itemtype="http://schema.org/Recipe" class="schemaRecipeContainer">
	<div class="schemaRecipeNameAuthorDate">
		<span itemprop="name" class="schemaRecipeName">Chocolate Strawberry Shots</span>
		<span class="schemaRecipeDatePublished"><meta itemprop="datePublished" content="2016-7-13"></meta>July 13, 2016</span>
	</div>
	<span itemprop="description" class="schemaRecipeDescription">These are the easiest to make and the most delicious to consume. Perhaps they will replace the Jell-O shot at your next gathering?</span>
	<div class="schemaRecipeIngredientsHeader">Ingredients</div>
		<ul class="schemaRecipeIngredients"><li itemprop="ingredients">
				Strawberries
			</li>
			<li itemprop="ingredients">
				Chocolate liqueur, such as Godiva Dark
			</li>
		</ul><div class="schemaRecipeInstructionsHeader">Recipe Instructions</div>
	<span itemprop="recipeInstructions" class="schemaRecipeInstructions">
		<ol><li>
				To make the shot glasses, remove the stem and cut just enough of the end off of the strawberry so it can stand. Using a small spoon, remove the inner flesh, taking care not to poke through the bottom. To make the shot, fill your strawberry shot glass with the chilled chocolate liqueur of your choice. Enjoy!
			</li>
		</ol></span>
	<div class="schemaRecipeCredits"><a href="http://www.bbqislandinc.com/rich-snippet-recipe-markup-tool.html">Recipe Generator</a> courtesy of BBQ Island</div>
</div>]]></description><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117196/instagram-food-drink-emoji" title="Instagram's Most Common Food &amp;amp; Drink Emoji Reveal We Really Like Booze"><media:thumbnail url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/950/x,80/1623259/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117195/coloring-book-cookbook" title="Coloring Book Cookbooks Are A Thing Now"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/5e3/x,80/1623258/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><link rel="related" type="text/html" href="http://www.refinery29.com/2016/07/117096/100-years-family-dinners-mode" title="Dine Back In Time With 100 Years Of Family Dinners"><media:thumbnail url="http://s3.r29static.com//bin/entry/3cb/x,80/1622557/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></link><dc:creator>Claire Lower</dc:creator><dc:creator>Recipe by Claire Lower</dc:creator><publishedDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 18:20:00 +0000</publishedDate><updatedDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 19:39:51 +0000</updatedDate><media:content url="http://s1.r29static.com//bin/entry/cf0/1200x900,80/1621066/image.jpg" width="1200" height="900" type="image/jpeg"/><media:content url="https://content.jwplatform.com/videos/bgFne0IG-r0yi2e87.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="42" height="1080" width="1920"><media:title><![CDATA[Chocolate Strawberry Shots]]></media:title><media:category>Food,Living,Recipe</media:category><media:thumbnail url="https://content.jwplatform.com/thumbs/bgFne0IG-720.jpg"/></media:content></item></channel></rss>
